<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="Artworks.xsl"?>

<Artworks>

  <artwork_id>1</artwork_id>
  <images_id>6</images_id>
  <imagel_id>6</imagel_id>
  <artist_id>6</artist_id>
  <genre_id>6</genre_id>
  <subject_id>2</subject_id>
  <dimensions>N/A</dimensions>
  <location>N/A</location>
  <artwork_name>De Matteis Triumph of the Immaculate Anagoria</artwork_name>
  <price>200000000</price>
  <artwork_date>c. 1710 - 1715</artwork_date>
  <artwork_type>Fresco</artwork_type>
  <description>
    <p>A baroque era fresco painting by Paolo De Matteis.</p>
  </description>
  <more_info>
    <p>Difficult to extract, but worth the price.</p>
  </more_info>

  <artwork_id>2</artwork_id>
  <images_id>7</images_id>
  <imagel_id>7</imagel_id>
  <artist_id>2</artist_id>
  <genre_id>3</genre_id>
  <subject_id>2</subject_id>
  <dimensions>280cm x 570cm</dimensions>
  <location>Sistine Chapel Ceiling</location>
  <artwork_name>The Creation of Adam</artwork_name>
  <price>300000</price>
  <artwork_date>c. 1512</artwork_date>
  <artwork_type>Fresco</artwork_type>
  <description>
    <p>Pretty thirsty for knowledge, The Creation of Adam by Michelangelo is a fresco painting any ceiling enthusiast will want in their collection. Price does not include extraction.</p>
  </description>
  <more_info>
    <p>Illustrates the the biblical creation narrative from the bible where God gives life to the first man, Adam. The near touching hands of God and Adam becomes the iconic of humanity.</p>
  </more_info>

  <artwork_id>3</artwork_id>
  <images_id>8</images_id>
  <imagel_id>8</imagel_id>
  <artist_id>1</artist_id>
  <genre_id>1</genre_id>
  <subject_id>1</subject_id>
  <dimensions>77cm x 53cm</dimensions>
  <location>Musee du Louvre, Paris</location>
  <artwork_name>Mona Lisa</artwork_name>
  <price>1000000000</price>
  <artwork_date>c. 1503 - 1506</artwork_date>
  <artwork_type>Oil on Poplar Panel</artwork_type>
  <description>
    <p>Renowned for her smile, this is the famous Mona Lisa. The Mona Lisa is a half-length portrait painting by the Italian Renaissance artist Leonardo da Vinci.</p>
  </description>
  <more_info>
    <p>The Mona Lisa is widely reknowned around the world. It is one of the most valuable paintings in the world. The painting is assumed to be the portrait of Lisa Gherardini the wife of Francesco del Giocondo.</p>
    <p>The expression of Mona Lisa is often described as enigmatic, as the atmospheric illusionism, subtle modelling of the forms contribute to continuing fascination to this day.</p>
  </more_info>

  <artwork_id>4</artwork_id>
  <images_id>9</images_id>
  <imagel_id>9</imagel_id>
  <artist_id>7</artist_id>
  <genre_id>1</genre_id>
  <subject_id>2</subject_id>
  <dimensions>330cm x 550cm</dimensions>
  <location>Sistine Chapel</location>
  <artwork_name>The Delivery of the Keys to Saint Peter</artwork_name>
  <price>999999</price>
  <artwork_date>c. 1481 - 1482</artwork_date>
  <artwork_type>Fresco</artwork_type>
  <description>
    <p>From the classical Italian Renaissance era painter Pietro Perugino comes a masterpiece of epic proportions. Part of the world famous Sistine Chapel next to the more famous painting by Michelangelo, The Delivery of the Keys to Saint Peter is a
      magnificent piece of art to add to any collection.</p>
  </description>
  <more_info>
    <p>The work originated from when Perugino was decorating a chapel in Rome and the pope; Pope Sixtus IV was pleased by his work. The pope comissioned Perugino and other artists in the formation of this artwork to be used as a decoration of a new
      chapel build in the Vatican.</p>
  </more_info>

  <artwork_id>5</artwork_id>
  <images_id>10</images_id>
  <imagel_id>10</imagel_id>
  <artist_id>5</artist_id>
  <genre_id>2</genre_id>
  <subject_id>3</subject_id>
  <dimensions>73.7cm x 92.1cm</dimensions>
  <location>Museum of Modern Art, New York City</location>
  <artwork_name>The Starry Night</artwork_name>
  <price>300000000</price>
  <artwork_date>1889</artwork_date>
  <artwork_type>Oil on Canvas</artwork_type>
  <description>
    <p>The art of art - the Starry Night is an oil on canvas created by the Dutch post-impressionist by Vincent van Gogh, it is the art work that all art thieves want to thief. No collection of art is complete without this art of all arts.</p>
  </description>
  <more_info>
    <p>The painting depicts the view from the east-facing window of the asylum room at Saint-Remy-De-Provence, just before sunrise with the image of an idealized village.</p>
  </more_info>

</Artworks>